{
  "categories": [],
  "description": " Fill the blanks in these English language idioms. ",
  "difficulty": -1,
  "questions": [{
    "answer": "moon",
    "category": "English Idioms Quiz",
    "question": "Once in a blue ____"
  }, {
    "answer": "least",
    "category": "English Idioms Quiz",
    "question": "Last, but not _____"
  }, {
    "answer": "one",
    "category": "English Idioms Quiz",
    "question": "Back to square ___"
  }, {
    "answer": "tree",
    "category": "English Idioms Quiz",
    "question": "Barking up the wrong ____"
  }, {
    "answer": "bell",
    "category": "English Idioms Quiz",
    "question": "Saved by the ____"
  }, {
    "answer": "goose",
    "category": "English Idioms Quiz",
    "question": "Wild _____ chase"
  }, {
    "answer": "colors",
    "category": "English Idioms Quiz",
    "question": "Pass with flying ______"
  }, {
    "answer": "bush",
    "category": "English Idioms Quiz",
    "question": "Beating around the ____"
  }, {
    "answer": "bite",
    "category": "English Idioms Quiz",
    "question": "All bark and no ____"
  }, {
    "answer": "riches",
    "category": "English Idioms Quiz",
    "question": "From rags to ______"
  }, {
    "answer": "pours",
    "category": "English Idioms Quiz",
    "question": "When it rains, it _____"
  }, {
    "answer": "leaf",
    "category": "English Idioms Quiz",
    "question": "Turn over a new ____"
  }, {
    "answer": "foot",
    "category": "English Idioms Quiz",
    "question": "Put one's best ____ forward"
  }, {
    "answer": "sight",
    "category": "English Idioms Quiz",
    "question": "A _____ for sore eyes"
  }, {
    "answer": "teeth",
    "category": "English Idioms Quiz",
    "question": "Through gritted _____"
  }, {
    "answer": "drawing",
    "category": "English Idioms Quiz",
    "question": "Back to the _______ board"
  }, {
    "answer": "shoulder",
    "category": "English Idioms Quiz",
    "question": "Chip on one's ________"
  }, {
    "answer": "form",
    "category": "English Idioms Quiz",
    "question": "Any way, shape, or ____"
  }, {
    "answer": "path",
    "category": "English Idioms Quiz",
    "question": "Off the beaten ____"
  }, {
    "answer": "yards",
    "category": "English Idioms Quiz",
    "question": "The whole nine _____"
  }, {
    "answer": "hard place",
    "category": "English Idioms Quiz",
    "question": "Between a rock and a ____ _____"
  }, {
    "answer": "horse",
    "category": "English Idioms Quiz",
    "question": "Beat a dead _____"
  }, {
    "answer": "cows",
    "category": "English Idioms Quiz",
    "question": "'Til the ____ come home"
  }, {
    "answer": "cigar",
    "category": "English Idioms Quiz",
    "question": "Close but no _____"
  }, {
    "answer": "both ends",
    "category": "English Idioms Quiz",
    "question": "Burn the candle at ____ ____"
  }, {
    "answer": "resistance",
    "category": "English Idioms Quiz",
    "question": "Path of least __________"
  }, {
    "answer": "silent",
    "category": "English Idioms Quiz",
    "question": "The strong, ______ type"
  }, {
    "answer": "Bats",
    "category": "English Idioms Quiz",
    "question": "____ in the belfry"
  }, {
    "answer": "tacks",
    "category": "English Idioms Quiz",
    "question": "Get down to brass _____"
  }, {
    "answer": "hog",
    "category": "English Idioms Quiz",
    "question": "Living high on the ___"
  }],
  "quizLength": 30,
  "title": "English Idioms Quiz",
  "url": "http://www.jetpunk.com/quizzes/english-idioms-quiz.php"
}